a big red flag for me is if I don't have
anything in common like hobby wise with
somebody like it's it's such a necessary
relationship trait to have I think it's
so easy to be physically attracted to
somebody obviously it's everyone's first
instinct but I think if you want
longevity in in a relationship you have
to have that extra layer of
compatibility right you you have to want
to do things together I think so like a
a big red flag for me is like if a girl
doesn't go to the gym and that's just
because it's a very big part of my life
I I love going I go every day I'm a very
big advocate of going to the gym and
working out it's so good for your health
not just your physical but your mental
health as well get your endorphins going
get some of that stress relief out of
you you know but I do acknowledge that
it's it's not for everybody it's it's
intimidating for some people who don't
go every day and I try to be cognizant
of that and I try to help out the best I
can like there may be there may be some
people in here right now maybe watching
at home that want to get started and
just don't know how to take that first
step and if there is anybody out there I
I highly recommend the program I just
started about 6 months months ago that
changed my life forever and that that
program is where I
only work out with black
dudes
exclusively because black dudes will
push you to your limits whether you want
to or not I started about 6 months ago
man I was in the gym one day and I was
having a bad day I was I was stressed
about something I was angry about
something and I was like man [__] this
I'm I'mma use this negative as a
positive I'm going to use this
aggression I'mma put up some weight and
I was hitting a chest day so I was like
[__] it I'm going hit a new Max on the
on the bench press so I go in there put
the lighter weights on first get
loosened up get warm you know then then
you got to put on the heavier stuff and
when you do that you're supposed to have
a
um yeah yeah spotter so you don't
die and I didn't know anybody in there
at the time closest person to me was the
black dude at the bench next to me so I
walked over I was like hey man would you
uh would you mind spotting me for this
set real quick and he was
like yeah I got
you I was like I feel like you
do everything about your voice is safe I
feel like I can lift the world now okay
come on so we so we go over to the bench
together he he gets behind the rack in
the spot position he's ready I lay down
and I'm trying to psych myself up get in
the zone line up my hands get a good
grip and finally I just finally I just I
get it off the rack
oh I
get one rep
in oh I
get two reps in I get I I get stuck on
the third my my my arm start
shaking and he can see
this so like any good
spotter he has some words of
encouragement I'm trying not to die and
this man just gets in my ear
and do that
[__] do that [__] it ain't nothing I was
like I said I don't know man I'm I'm
getting kind of tired he was like my
people being tired I was like God
damn I'm sorry
it was only like 255 you had white guilt
on top of that it's like 500 lb man I
was like is this pre-workout or a
history lesson what are we doing
dog [__] I racked that [__] up I was
like I appreciate you man I was
struggling at the end he was like you
don't know
struggle [__] man can't have
anything so that's my new routine
whenever somebody's like you look good
Matt you want a diet like yeah it's
called white watch you should try
it so when black people watch white
people struggle you will sweat I promise
you this is one of the whitest crowds
I've ever seen in my entire life bro I'm
uncomfortable yall are so is this a
comedy show or I'm meeting God damn oh
my gosh I'm
sorry ref flag number m
H we could try something
different this could be fun or it could
be a [__]
nightmare but I think we can have fun um
so the thing is it's like I could do red
flags for hours we and they could be
funny we could all laugh have a
guaranteed good time but who wants to do
that so and a lot of times I don't like
to do a lot of red flags because it it
is very male to female you know it's
it's it's listing things that men don't
like about women and I don't want that
to be unfair one-sided or sexist so to
even it out sometimes I am genuinely
curious like for the women in the
audience what might be some red flags
for a guy if you go on a date with him
he says or does this that makes you kind
of be like uh I don't
[Applause]
know hold I'm going go I'm going go
balcony I'm going go balcony what is it
is it a good one I don't know splitting
the check splitting the
check okay
splitting the check uh on a first
date he asked in the beginning of the
date middle of the day towards the
middle oh you were
boring in the middle can I get you
anything yeah two checks two checks
would be great yeah yeah yeah so where
did you say you were
from F how how recently was this oh 5
months ago 5 months ago okay and you
still upset um
so hold on where where where did you
where did you go to
eat uh temp what is it the and Temple
the Jen and Temple what is
[Applause]
that
rude what kind of restaurant is that I
me have catfish on
steak Yeah catfish and steak
it's like a roadh house an expensive
roadh house okay yeah I mean maybe did
you like him until that moment did you
like him
[Applause]
no I'm curious I'm curious until he
asked us with the check were you're like
this is going
good you
were
[Music]
[__] oh my God let me did you sleep with
him
yes
wow oh my
God he split you and the check in one
[Applause]
night oh my
god did he leave a big til
[Applause]
what that was an unnecessary detail what
you
say I said he was sweaty when we did it
he was sweaty after yeah my man was
putting in
work that's just that's that's good I
would
think [__] well
I'm sorry you got half of a meal
sorry all right we're one for one what's
another fun
[Applause]
one do you have a fun
one what is
it
hor he's huge and does steroids
[Music]
oh this is going to get cancelable
let's do
it so you said when he says he's on
hormone therapy but he's just [__]
jacked so hormone therapy what's that
supposed to do balance it out basically
so what he says he has too much like
natural testosterone no he doesn't have
enough he doesn't have
enough okay how long have you been
seeing this
Man 2 25 years
[Applause]
oh what where did you meet
him you met him when you guys were kids
so he tells you he's going on hormone
therapy to to to get more testosterone
but you think he you think he's on
steroids you know so did you find them
yes could you get me
some I'm trying to get in gay shape dog
let's go I'm taking all the
shortcuts did you you did find some was
is it a needle or a pill he is gay
shap she said she thinks he is in gay
shape the plot
thickens oh my
God this is this is the bigger red flag
now buddies he has his workout buddies
do you have a picture of him I want to
see if I want to see what his gar says
about oh [__] God damn it the phones are
locked
up God
damn your phone isn't a hormone blocker
God damn
it okay after the show I want to see
this yeah I mean that's a valid refle
you don't want somebody who's lying
about an obvious appearance thing like
if you're clearly on steroid just own up
to the [__] it's fine it's fine to do it
if that's if that's the body you want
the life you want to live you can can
[__] do that it's fine as long as you
can still get your dick up you
fine he can't then it's not okay stop
with you're doing immediately stop
seeing
you
okay let's unlock our
phone can we unlock your
[Applause]
phone okay okay okay
okay okay
okay bro what if it's just a of
me Eric's like unlock the phone and I'm
like nah we don't got to do all that we
don't got to let's just take her word
for
it oh my God that's it that's what you
unlock him with that [__] Flying
Saucer can I may may I see your phone
there we go pass it over oh this is
great this better be worth
it there we go pass that back to her
there we go I just I just got to see a
picture of this guy and then I want see
what you
think I want to test this gar let's
go God
damn bro he has the traps that my
grandpa's Pocket [__] wishes it
[Applause]
had oh my
God why is his neck so
big oh my God this [__] looks so
unsure okay resident
gay what are we thinking what are we
[Music]
thinking what is it what what is it the
pose the pose he's gay ding ding ding
ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
[Applause]
any excuse to drink go
ahead now this is go whenever we out a
gay an angel gets his wings this is good
this is good everybody knows
that you know what's [__] up I've
posed like that before so I was like
[Music]